Hello everyone my name is Mie and I am from Vietnam.
My name is Tien and I'm from Vietnam. We are part of the
Cardano Eastern Townhall
Also the moderator and translator of the Vietnam Townhall.
It’s exciting that Cardano has spread its wing to East Asia
and create more opportunities and roles to equalize
the community and build up the decentralization system.
It connects East Asia with the world.
Catalyst project is growing fast with the number of
proposals increasing double every fund
if we could optimize all the votes from ADA holders, the
chance you get funded for a project is higher.
Especially when the majority of the ADA holder is in Asia
However, there is a language barrier for those non-native
English-speaking countries.
It is difficult for them to fully understand the insight of
the proposal and might easily overlook them
and only vote along with the crowd.
Our proposal is "Connecting Asian Voters and Proposers."
Our goal is to establish a process, format, and event stage
for voter and proposer onboarding.
To bring voters, proposers, and proposals closer together by
building trust between them.
This can be approached in many ways help ADA holders
understand why it is important to vote
give translation guidelines, socialize content, and conduct
routine surveys.
I believe there will be many efficient ways to achieve the
goal and you might be the one to bring it up.
So help us improve decision-making across the Eastern
Hemisphere by making Catalyst voting more accessible.
Thank you very much