hello people of arcardano my name is jan
a representative of the eastern town
hall and also an entrepreneur
thank you for your precious time it is
very much appreciated it is my intention
to provide to you the viewers a
manifestation of our passion to grow
cardano to its maximum collaboration
potential
the proposal i will share with you is
called connecting with east asian
entrepreneurs from japan korea
vietnam indonesia and so many other
countries
our challenge theme is the category
proposal outreach with our requested
funds of twenty thousand dollars
this proposal is a joint effort by
various project catalyst veteran
community members that have converged
and collaborated on the creation of the
eastern town hall
you can communicate with us freely at
our various communication channels you
can find in our slide
eastern town hall foundations is the
embryo of this proposal
the problem that we have clearly
identified is that there are no
initiatives to attract and engage east
asian entrepreneurs
where they are in their local language
this can simply be seen in the
participation of east asian
entrepreneurs in project catalyst fund
six although a record-breaking 800 plus
proposal submitted
there was only 17 proposals from vietnam
seven from japan and only one from
indonesia a country with 52 million
economically secured citizens
our thoughtful solution to this problem
is by using the eastern town hall and
various specifically targeted virtual
events to establish and support a
network of east asian entrepreneurs
we want to reach their massive untapped
potential
meet them where they are in their
country their language and their culture
where they can build knowledge share
information connect and support each
other
thinking global acting local the team
behind all this collaborative effort
brings a wealth of cultural and
technical experience to cardano
we are all very active in catalysts and
community groups across our ecosystem
we are a diverse group united by the
promise of cardano
we have utah from japan our cardano
ambassador and certified public
accountant we have myself from indonesia
an eastern town hall community leader
for indonesia and entrepreneur we have
mitran from vietnam an english and
international business major with
experience working with western
businesses we have robert o'brien from
new zealand a financial systems software
engineer
community co-organizer and entrepreneur
we have felix weber from france a
community manager building bridges
between people also a member of caddo
circle kettle swarm and catalyst school
there are also so many other members
that i refrain from mentioning to only
to time limitations
our proposal is about running virtual
events in january or february of 2022 to
develop entrepreneurs in vietnam and
indonesia the event aims to upskill
entrepreneurs to develop market
opportunities based on cardano
the purpose of the event is to build
startup founders and distributed
autonomous organization collaborators
our tent is to educate focus on
experience-based learning by providing a
soft way for the general public to
access entrepreneurship and blockchain
technology without risk with plans to
finish on conclusion of the second week
of catalyst 8 february 2022 teams will
be submitting proposals to catalyst fund
8 as part of their work
at the end of the event at least 15
teams have managed to complete the
process and submitted proposals to
catalyst fund 8.
individuals complete the event with new
skills connections and inspiration to
continue their cardano journey
thank you so much for your time and we
humbly ask for your vote you can find
our proposals in the following links of
our slide please do ask any questions
and we would love to provide answers and
assurance let us grow cardano to even
greater heights by growing east asia
with us as your tool